本作品由 NORM TEAM 荣誉出品
下载后仅供学习交流,严禁用于商业途径
更多精彩 尽在 www.normteam.com
压制: mzj5212  字幕:mzj5212
各位观众, 从刚才细腻的画面来看
Ladies and gentlemen, from the picture,
你们不想而知
you can tell easily that
这个一定是我的梦中情人
she is my dream lover
为了打动她的芳心, 看来我恐怕要在她面前
To impress her, I'd take this chance
展示我的小小绝技了
I'll show her some of my martial arts
咦，她不为物质所动哦!
She is not touched!
回来!
Come back!
看来这时间没有女孩...
No girls...
不喜欢这件事情
will refuse such things
都警告你28年了!
I've told you for 28 years!
你不能喜欢这个女孩
You can't fall for that girl
你到底是谁?
Who are you?
为什么你次次都要阻止我寻梦?
Why do you stop me from dreaming?
我不想再看到你!
I don't want to see you!
好呀! 送你一程!
OK! I'll send you back to your world!
闭嘴!
Shut up!
又在做28年同样的那个梦?
The same dream? You've dreamt it for 28 years!
是啊. 但是我就是不知道为什么....
Yes. But I don't know why...
我想那个女孩肯定是喜欢你了
I think the girl is fond of you,
如果不是这样的话，怎么会每晚都来找你呢？
otherwise she won't come to your dream every night
我想也是这样. 但是每次她都走得那么快
I think so. But she'll leave soon
看看你现在这个样子! 干爹!
Look at you! My God-father!
你再不收拾整齐点的话,
If you don't dress well,
不要说女孩子，我都想走啊!
I do want to leave you! You know?
为了留下你们两个
To keep you and my dream lover to stay with me
我要振作!
I'll change!
今天练习什么?
What'll we practise today?
龙卷旋风脚!
Make it ABC!
龙卷旋风...
AB...
脚!
C!
聪明!
Smart boy!
警报响了!
The alarm!
什么事呢?
What's the matter?
看看去
Go and search for it
好!
OK!
哎，你换错衣服了!
You've mistaken it!
sorry! sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
准备好了没?
Ready?
好了!
Yes!
换位!
Change position!
跳!
Jump!
到你了!
Your turn!
你下来啊!
Come on!
到你了!
Your turn!
我来了!
I'm coming!
我们进去看一下
I'll go and have a look
这里好黑啊!
This is so dark!
你看到什么了?
Can you see anything?
我看到了!
Yes I do!
你到底看到什么了?
What have you seen?
哦! 有些东西!
Oh! There's something!
别理是什么东西了!
Forget it!
总之就是些什么东西!
Just take it easy!
到底什么呢?
What?
开灯
Turn on the light
什么?
What?
到底什么?
What is it?
你看看!
Look!
我想是博士又做错了什么吧
I think, Doctor must have done something wrong
如果不是, 他不会吓唬我们的
If not, he would not have scared us
那我们等他出来
Let's wait for his appearance
出来吧!
Come out!
博士，我知道你在这!
I know you are here!
有什么事情你跟我们说嘛!
Just tell us what's in your mind!
你们这些前辈做错了事情
What you've done wrong
我们这些做后辈的, 一定不会责怪你的
I'm your God-son, I'll give you face
那好我出来，你们不许打我
Well, don't beat me, OK?
行!
OK!
对不起! 我错了!
I'm sorry! I did something wrong!
那你做错了什么?
What is it?
尽管说出来
Just go ahead
我...
I...
讲啊!
Come on!
我昨晚在市场那里不见了5分硬币
I lost 5 cents yesterday in the market
你!?
You!?
去死吧!
Go to hell!
怎么就不见了5分硬币呢!
How can you lose 5 cents!
岂有此理!
Damn it!
你知道错了吗?
Do you know it's your fault?
知道了, 我知道错了...
Yes, I do...
如果你找不回来的话
If you can't find it back
那就见你一次，教训你一次了
I'll teach you good lessons until you get it back
坏了! 我们走!
Shit! Let's go!
我终于找到了!
I've got it back!
这次轮到我了!
My turn now!
来，吃早餐!
Come and eat breakfast!
你的，你的...
Yours...
你们两个为什么不吃?
Why don't you eat?
都被你教训了一顿了
You've taken revenge, haven't you?
不至于这样对我们吧?
Are you kidding?
虽然我们误会了你
Although we misunderstood you,
但你知道我正在发育的嘛!
you know I'm growing!
给这么小的鸡蛋我，怎么够吃？
It's not enough for me to eat such a small egg
蛋不是用来吃的，是用来做试验的!
This is not for your breakfast but for our experiment!
什么?
What?
别玩了?
Kidding?
做试验?
For experiment?
我告诉你, 如果试验成功
I tell you, if it is successful
肯定会吃撑死你们的
lt'll be enough for few meals of yours
我不相信
I won't believe it
so am l!
So am I!
你们不相信?
Don't you?
那我试给你们看一下!
I'll show you now!
这个是我的最新发明
This is my newest invention
不就是个放大镜吗!
It's microscope!
没错, 这个是放大镜
Yes, it is
不过不是普通放大镜
But it's not a common one
是经过我精雕细凿,精心设计 它是...
I've taken long time to design it, it is...
荒谬!
Ridiculous!
它就是我精益求精研究出来的超级放大镜!
It's a super microscope made by me!
只要按这个键,
Touch this button,
放在任何物体的上面
put it above an object
就会产生变化, 看!
All will be changed, see!
看看!
See!
还不是放大了!
It's microscope!
就是啊
Yes
仔细看!
Look!
我成功了!
I'm successful!
看来这次真的够营养了!
It's enough for any kind of growth!
这都被你做到了!
He really makes it!
看来好几天我们都不用吃了
But what a pity that we can't take other food for few days
我怎么就还没吃饱呢!
I don't feel I'm full!
不够饱? 那我用放大镜来帮帮你
What? Let me help you with your new invention
这儿说找宝藏有钱分！
Here is an attractive advertisement
兼职!
Part time job!
1000万!
To earn over 10 millions!
发达了
We're going to be rich
我这本呢...
This is the scroll...
是记载所有江湖传说的宝书
which recorded all legends of the world
这篇就是喇嘛经
This is the Sutra of Lama
这篇也是
So is it
这篇特别点
This is special
是什么?
What is it?
还是喇嘛经
This is the Sutra of Lama too
shit!
Shit!
这些呢?
How about this?
这个厉害了!
It's great!
这个就是我们要找的雪山宝藏
This is the treasure we are going to find out
这个就是玉女峰
This is the Virgin's Mountain
据经文记载, 在玉女峰之颠...
From the scroll, it's stated that...
埋藏着玉女寒冰
The Virgin's Ice is hidden
如果我们找到玉女寒冰
If we can get the Virgin's Ice
我们就可以从魔宫那里...
We can change it for big money...
换到一笔数目可观的奖金了
from the Evil's Palace
到时候不但是发财,
If we breathe in the "Essence Air",
简直是可以长生不老了
we can live forever
等一下!
Wait!
又怎么了?
What's the matter?
如果我们的计划失败了
Our stuff maybe stolen if we are leaving
又找不到那块冰
if we can't get the ice
到时候又不见了这里的东西的话,
Then,
我们岂不是偷鸡不成蚀把米!
we'll suffer double loss!
是啊?
Right?
是不是
That is
你同不同意?
So you agree?
不用担心!
Don't worry!
有我的新发明...
My new invention...
特别超浓缩二合一暂时视觉阻碍空间液体
two to one vision obstruction liquid
有了这东西, 什么都搞定!
With its help, it'll be fine!
那是什么东西?
What is it?
特别超浓缩二合一暂时视觉阻碍空间液体...
Two to one...
简称隐形水, 明不明白?
It makes things invisible, got it?
明白明白!
Got you!
做你该做的事!
Do your work!
已经搞定了!
It's fixed!
不是吧?
What's wrong?
出发!
Let's go!
这隐形水真是厉害!
The liquid is really great!
那不是连钱都没有了?
How about the money? Destroyed?
我只是把它们全部隐形了!
I've solution to make it visible!
出发!
Let's go!
添仔!
Hey Tim!
这边!
This way!
来了!
I'm coming!
快点!
Hurry up!
不等你了!
We won't wait for you!
等等我!
Wait for me!
博士, 是不是这儿?
Doctor, isn't it here?
根据经书记载, 玉女峰山脚下有个生命终站
It's stated that, below the Virgin's Mountain, there is a Life Terminal
没错! 就是这里!
Yes! It's right!
让我看一下
Let me have a look
这边有个葫芦
It's stated that there is a calabash and
葫芦上面有个BAR字
a word "bar" next to it
是这里了!
It's the location stated!
那我们出去吧!
Let's go!
好啊!
OK!
不行, 有飞机朝我们开过来了!
No, there is a plane flying towards us!
这边行不行？
We can't take this way!
不行! 有人过来了
No! Someone is coming
那这边呢?
How about this side?
还是不行!
No!
这边有架摩托车!
There are motor cycles!
牛啊! 汽车也饮水？
Great! A car is drinking water
有什么出奇的? 那边还有马饮汽油呢
What so funny? There is a horse drinking oil
是真的啊! 看来我们要找另外的出口了
It's real! We'd find another exit
为什么?
Why?
车来了!
There is car!
怎么称呼你?
May I know your name?
ruby!
Ruby!
你想点什么歌?
What song would you like?
我想点'梦中情人'
I want to hear "Dream Lover"
点给你的梦中情人听的吧?
For you dream lover?
但是他是不存在的!
But he is not existing!
我是不是很傻?
Am I silly?
傻或者不傻, 在情人的眼中是没有分别的!
Silly or not, it's of no difference now!
为什么他是一个不存在的人呢?
Why is he not existing?
都说是梦中情人了!
Because he is my dream lover!
那他又怎么会出现在现实世界里面呢
So he is not existing in my world
那么你的梦中情人,
About your dream lover,
他是不是好可爱...
is he having...
又或者很有型，说来听听?
any visible figure?
当然很有型了!
Sure!
他的体形就好象...
He is as strong as...
阿诺德施瓦辛格健硕
Arnold Schewazeniger
他的样子呢就好像 michael fox
He's having a baby face as Michael Fox
他的身材就好像里察基尔般标准
He is as tall as Richard Gere
他的风度就象汤姆克鲁斯这么有魅力
He is as charm as Tom Cruise
我最喜欢的就是他的鹰勾鼻
I love his Roman nose most
这么完美的组合! 世界上再也找不出这么出色的男人了
What a perfect match! I think it's hard to find one in this world
谁说不是呢!
That's right!
那么你还是多做梦吧
So you've to make more dreams
我也知道只有做梦才能见到他
I know I can only see him in my dream
ruby小姐, 你在做什么?
Miss Ruby, what are you doing?
博士, 怎么样? 太高了
Doctor, how can we get up? It's too high
我想这里没车了吧
I think there won't be any car
前面有些白忽忽的东西, 不知道是什么呢?
This is something white in front, what is it?
出什么事情了?
What's the matter?
没事! 我吓走它了!
Nothing! I've just scared it away!
好了，我们上去吧!
Let's go up!
这个出口对不对?
Is it the correct exit?
宝书上好像是这么写的!
It's written in the scroll!
喂，等等我!
Wait for me!
哎呀，岂有此理!
Damn it!
看完本小姐洗澡就这么走了!
They just sneak away after peeping my bath!
让你尝一下我的夺命剪刀脚! 去死吧!
Try my Super Scissors legs! Go to hell!
是什么东西飞过来了?
What is it?
这么快就不见了？
It disappears soon!
刚才我明明看见有什么东西飞过来的!
I've seen something flying towards me!
我也看到了!
Me too!
也许是鬼吧! 快点走了!
Maybe it's ghost! Let's go!
回去一定要查查宝书
I've to worship God when we go back
快点走啊!
Let's go!
来了!
I'm coming!
你怎么样? miss ruby?
How are you? Miss Ruby?
没什么, 我好像见到我的梦中情人了
I'm fine, I think I've just seen my dream lover
不过他好像缩水了好多
But he is a little bit short
别那么挑剔嘛! 可能是个机会啊
Don't be that selective! It's a rare chance
你说得对! 我要把握这个机会
You're right! I've to make use of this chance
别生气
Don't get angry
会伤身的！
lt'll harm your health
别生气了,
Don't be that angry,
好伤身的
it'll harm your health
施主，千万别生气!
Don't be that angry!
喂，有人偷东西!
Someone is stealing!
哪儿?
Where?
等等我! 别走那么快!
Wait for me! Don't go that fast!
不要啊!
Stop it!
你新来的?
Are you new?
你知道你的工作是什么吗?
Do you know your job?
那就是不知道了
That means you don't know
看! 下面的男人都是想...
Look! All the men want...
上玉女峰拿玉女寒冰的
to get the Virgin's Ice
你没讲给她听的吗?
Haven't you told her?
我在听你讲啊
I'll let you tell her
不过从来都没有一个男人...
No one can...
可以从玉女峰安全返回的
return safely
为什么?
Why?
好简单! 根本就不可能上去到玉女峰
It's simple! It's impossible for them to get to the Virgin's Mountain
并且根本就不能在天黑之前拿到玉女寒冰回来
And any of them can get the ice before sunset
与其让那些花花绿绿的钞票
Therefore,
在山上陪伴那些死人骨头
why not take their money?
那不如把它放到我们的口袋里!
Or, their money will just stay in the mountain with their skeleton!
那不是骗人吗?
That means cheating?
骗人?
Cheating?
当然不是! 是技巧
No! It's technique
那需不需要牺牲色相?
Should I seduce them?
我们这儿是生命终站
Here is the Life Terminal
就是说这些男人明天就魂归天国
That means the men will go to heaven tomorrow
你就当是做善事好了
Just take it as beneficence
另外就是, 那个...
And, leave the man...
鹰勾鼻的男人的善事我来做
with Roman nose to me
这种清凉的感觉,
Such cool feeling,
才能迷倒我
I can get from him only
帅哥，我好喜欢你的鹰勾鼻
I love your Roman nose
我最恨人家碰我的鼻子
I hate others mentioning my Roman nose
活该!
You deserve it!
看看周围!
Serve you right!
看来都没人是我们的对手
No one is capable of being our opponent
我想反正他们上山,
I think even they can get to the top,
都拿不到那块冰回来
they still can't have the ice
不如我们抢劫光他们的钱?
Why don't we rob their money?
不行! 我们不能用这种卑鄙的手段
No! We can't use this way
不行啊？那我们偷好了
No! Then we can steal
不行!
No way!
我们不能做这种小人的行为
That's a very filthy behavior
这也不行啊! 无论怎样
Why not! Anyway
他们明天上雪山也不会回来的
They won't be able to come back alive after tomorrow
不如帮他们...
I want to help them...
保住那些钱啊
to keep their money
善哉! 善哉!
Good deed! Good deed!
周星驰?
Stephen Chow Sing-chi?
不, 我是...
No, I am...
周哈欠!
Tim Chow Ha-chi!
你笑什么?
What are you laughing?
周星驰也是这样粘上去的
Chow did the same
发错牌!
I've mistaken it!
我不是玩这种, 我是玩...
I don't want to play this, but...
猜牌!
Guessing game!
好, 我就和你赌100万
OK, let's bet a million
好，下注!
Deal!
添仔，我们没有那么多钱！
We don't have so much money to bet
赢定了!
Sure win!
赢定了?
Sure win?
好，下注!
Deal!
准备好!
Get ready!
1 , 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
7, 8, 9
你真笨啊? 怎么这么慢!
How poor are you? You're so slow!
你有钱输给别人吗?
Do you have money to pay?
你盖着什么牌了?
What did you cover?
9啊
It's a nine
真的是9吗？
Are you sure it's a nine
是!
Yes!
你肯定?
Sure?
当然!
Yes!
那就开出来看看!
Open it!
不是9 , 是一条线啊!
It's not nine, but there is a line!
我赢了!
Bingo!
她输了!
She lost!
好啊! 我赢了!
Bingo! I've make it!
我打遍天下无敌手!
I always win!
你这不是送钱给我花吗?
You mean giving me money?
这样，我明天不用走上山去了
So, I can hire somebody to carry me
我请人抬我上山了
instead of walking up to the Virgin's Mountain
那我们来猜先吧
Let's see who plays first
好
Sure
我要人头
I want head
好
OK
人头, 女士先
It's head, lady first
不好意思, 到我了
Sorry, me first
让你的
After you
我打40万一盘
Make the bet $500,000 for it
我想没人敢和我打了吧？
I don't think no one wants to play with me anymore
你错了! 还有我
You're wrong! I want to play with you
hi
Hi
让我尖叫, 让我心跳
To make me scream, to make my heart beats
是你一个灿烂的名字!
It's your name!
让我尖叫...
To make me scream...
末世天使?
The Angel of the corrupt age?
这位先生怎么称呼?
May I know your name?
以前人家叫我戴维斯
I was called Davis in the past
现在人家叫我亨得利
Now, I'm called Hungary
戴维斯亨得利，你要人头还是字?
Head or tail?
人头
Head
我要字
I want tail
怎么又这么大的味道?
What a strange smell?
快点!
It's fixed!
不好意思, 是我的
Sorry, it's mine
不要紧
Never mind
字, 我先来
Tail, me first
先生, 你卖艺吗?
Sir, are you martial-artist?
多嘴!
Don't be nosy!
球跑哪儿去了?
Where is the ball?
什么?
What?
sorry!
Sorry!
换球!
Change it!
怎么会这样呢?
How can it be?
你太大力了!
That's too powerful!
有道理! 有道理!
I see! I see!
看球!
Watch out!
不要生气, 会伤身的
Don't get angry, it'll harm your health
现在, 台面只剩下25分
Now, there are 25 marks left on the table
进了这个球, 我就赢定了
If I get that ball, I'll win
不好! 怎么办好呢?
Shit! What to do then?
我有办法
I've got any idea
超级放大镜!
Super microscope!
搞定!
It's fixed!
运气真好!
How lucky are you!
谢谢!
Thanks!
怎么了?
What is it?
没事!
Nothing!
超级放大镜
Super microscope
他好厉害!
He's smart!
这个稍微有点难度
This is quite difficult
bravo...
Bravo...
看来50万你是输定了
I think you'll lose that $500,000
多谢大家支持!
Thank you!
什么?
What?
我看50万你是输定了吧
You'll lose that $500,000
不过如果你没钱的话,
But if you don't have money,
你可以以身相许!
I'll take you in return!
你做梦!
Stop dreaming!
你小心打不中！
Watch out! Don't miss it
我就是不让你打
I won't let you hit it
我宁愿吃了它
I prefer eating it
有没有搞错?
Are you kidding?
快点把球吐出来
Give the ball back to me
快吐出来!
Give it now!
你真该死!
How bad you are!
超级无敌放大镜!
Super microscope!
我们是不是很酷呢?
Are we going too far?
到我了!
My turn!
球爆了!
The ball is broken!
换球!
Change it!
走开!
Get lost!
不高兴啊?
Can you stand it?
我想要出秘密武器了
I think I should use my own cue
干爹，我将全部洞口都放大了!
I've fixed up all the pockets!
这次靠你们两个了!
Thank you!
拿着!
Hold it!
要不要这样啊?
You mean it?
别废话!
Cut the crap!
来了!
Come on!
添仔, 顶住!
Tim, it's your turn!
这个中国仔真厉害!
The Chinese kid is really great!
最后的胜利属于我们!
We win at last!
不行!
My God!
抓住他们!
Arrest them!
走!
Go!
前无去路啊!
It's dead end!
你不可以走!
You can't go!
为什么?
Why?
因为你是我的梦中情人
Because you are my dream lover
现在怎么人人都这么说!
Many people love to use such excuse!
你白痴啊!
You are great!
你的梦中情人不是我
Your dream lover is not me
是 michael fox
It's should be Michael Fox
我说是就是!
You are my dream lover!
你说是就是吗?
Should I listen to you?
抓住他!
Arrest him!
走!
Go!
你不认是她的梦中情人的话, 我们就走不了了!
Admit it, or we can't escape!
认了吧!
Admit it!
先认了吧!
OK!
看来要出绝招了
Since we'd use this trick,
我要用血书以证心迹
I've to reveal my heart by writing a letter with my blood
接住!
Hold it!
你做过什么?
What have you done?
我帮你加速啊
I help you to increase your speed
真的吗?
Really?
你们可以走了!
You can go now!
这么有效?
Isn't it that kind of you?
不过要小心!
But be careful!
快点回来啊!
Come back!
她干什么?
What's it?
算了吧, 我们去找冰吧
Forget it, let's go for the Ice
没错，我们去寻梦
Let's go for the dream
走!
Go!
再见!
See you!
我会等你
I'll wait for you
我支持不住了!
I can stand any more!
你真没用!
You are useless!
让我来扶你
Let us help you
多谢!
Thank you!
不客气!
You are welcome!
你是老人家嘛!
Cause you are old!
我们是后辈, 应该的
We are young, so we'd help
干爹，你那块是什么味道?
What flavour is your food?
香蕉味, 你的呢?
Banana, what's yours?
我这块是榴莲味的
Mine has a flavour of durian
是吗? 我看看
Really? Let me try
不错!
Great!
不错吧?
Isn't it right?
是真的!
It's true!
水果冰?!
Mixed fruit punch?!
没什么味道嘛!
It's tasteless!
还说是博士，这样你都相信？
How can you believe such nonsense!
干爹博士，这儿是什么?
What was it in the past?
以前是条河
It was a river
如今是冰川
Now it's frozen
还有直升飞机!
A helicopter!
有人想给我们照相?
Someone wants to take our picture?
当然不是哪!
No!
他们知道我们一定会成功地拿到冰
They know we'll be successful in getting the Ice
所以就给我们做纪录嘛
So they are shooting the process for a TV special
是不是真的啊?
Are you kidding?
我认真的!
I am serious!
我的老天!
My God!
到时候我就出名了! 我会好忙!
Many people will know me! I'll be busy!
根据宝书记载
According to the scroll
过了这条河,
After this river,
我们会到一个很狭窄的山谷
we'll reach a narrow valley
是这儿吧?
Isn't it?
小心点
Be careful
小心! 注意那些冰屑
Watch out! Beware of slippery
进来了才说！
Forget it
小心点!
Be careful!
过了峡谷, 就到了一处峭壁
After the valley, then comes a cliff
小心被冰屑划伤!
Be careful of slippery!
不早点说?
Why didn't you warn me earlier?
你说的我们都经过了
What you've said, we all went through
宝书还有讲到什么吗?
What's next?
前面有个山坡
There is a slope ahead
过了山坡, 会见到一个小小的斜坡
After it, there is a slight slope too
然后沿着斜坡滑下
Just slide down
就到了!
That is!
走了!
Let's go!
小小斜坡在前面
The slope is just in front
下去吧!
Go down!
来了!
Come on!
真滑啊!
It's rather steep!
这个就是小小的斜坡?
Isn't it a slight slope?
还有多久才能到啊?
How long will it take?
根据宝书记载,
According to the scroll,
最快也要一个小时吧
it'll take over an hour
不是吧?
Kidding?
你不是说很快就可以到的吗？!
You've said we'd soon get there!
我真的不知道!
I don't know!
还有多远啊?
How far will it take?
你吹牛啊!
You liar!
宝书说的...
It's the scroll...
不要赖我!
which misleads me!
这里好冷!
It's cold!
小心你的头!
Watch out for your head!
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
我去探路!
I'll have a look!
小心点!
Be careful!
小孩子就是心急啊!
Kids always love speed!
我们去帮他!
Let's go to help!
好! 走了!
OK! Come on!
跟我来!
Follow me!
他去哪儿了?
Where has he gone?
这么眼熟? 是谁呢？
Who is he? He looks familiar to us
我想是裸体的添仔!
I think it's Tim, naked Tim!
穿上你的衣服!
Put on the clothes!
岂有此理!
Damn it!
脱我的衣服?
How dare you undress me?
我只是想帮你!
I just want to help!
是啊
Yes
什么时辰了?
What time is it?
11点了. 好黑啊!
11 o'clock. It's dark!
看来好危险!
It seems to be dangerous!
不如我们离开吧!
Let's leave here now!
什么?！
What?
根据宝书记载
The scroll stated that
我们来到这里正好是11点!
we'd get here by 11 o'clock!
真的?
Really?
真的! 走啊!
It's true! Let's go!
小心!
Watch out!
博士干爹
Doctor
我们明天再来好不好?
Shall we come tomorrow?
你不想发财吗?
Do you want to get rich?
要来你明天自己来好了
You can come yourself tomorrow
干爹!
God-father!
情人...
Ching Yan...
你还好吗?
Are you fine?
你怎么样?
How are you?
不用理我! 你们先走吧
Forget about me! You'd better leave now
你不用慌
Don't panic
我们回去搬救兵
I'll ask for help
不行, 我要留在这里陪干爹
No, I want to stay here to accompany him
好吧, 你就留在这里
Well, you can stay here
不行! 我要和你回去搬救兵
No! I want to go with you to seek help
那我们快去快回!
So, let's go, quick!
这种感觉在我梦里似曾相识!
I feel like staying in my dream!
坏了!
Shit!
我看不到东西了!
I can't see!
就快黑了
It is getting dark
我能支持下去吗?
Can I stand it?
情人!
Ching Yan!
你别睡啊! 起来!
You can't sleep! Get up!
坏了! 怎么叫都不醒!
My God! He falls asleep!
这样下去他一定会死的!
He'll be dead if he can't wake up!
不行，我要进去他的梦境!
I've to enter his dream!
情人, 快点起来!
Ching Yan, get up now!
情人!
Ching Yan!
起来!
Get up!
情人，我有危险! 起来!
I'm in danger! Get up!
他醒了!
He wakes up!
姑姑...
Madam...
不要过来
Don't come over
大王, 我观察了情况
Your Majesty, I've checked that
三个人取走了玉女寒冰
3 men have taken the Virgin's Ice
那就对了!
That's good!
我们现在该怎么办?
What'll we do now?
你们这帮蠢材!
You stupid ass!
等他们一下山, 就抢那块冰
When they come down, rob their Ice
明白!
Yes!
如果抢不回来的话
If you can't rob it
你们全部都得死!
All of you should die!
是
Yes sir
我们一定抢回来
We'll get it
愿大王长生不老
To give you the "Essence Air"
万寿无疆!
Long life to Your Majesty!
情人!
Ching Yan!
回答我!
Answer me!
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
他留下的鞋子!
He left the shoes!
留你的头啊!
You dumb bell!
他被雪盖着了! 快去救他!
He is covered by the snow! Go and save him!
别走那么快! 等等我!
Don't go that fast! Wait for me!
我要追上你才行
I've to catch you up
情人，你没事吧?
Are you fine?
干爹, 你没事吧?
God-father, are you OK?
情人
Ching Yan
干爹!
God-father!
有没有事?
Are you fine?
你没事吧?
Are you alright?
干爹，你没事吧?
Are you OK?
坏了! 他点头表示有事情啊
My God! He means yes by nodding his head
你这么打他没事也变成有事!
Look the way you're hitting him!
你发神经!
You idiot!
你有没有事啊?
Are you alright?
我没事!
I'm fine!
还是干爷爷你聪明!
You are great!
那还用说
Sure
你说什么?
What did you say?
玉女寒冰?
The Virgin's Ice?
在哪儿?
Where is it?
玉女寒冰!
The Virgin Ice!
这就是了!
That is!
就是那块! 带我过去啊!
That's it! Take me over there!
好美啊!
It's beautiful!
干爷爷，这块就是玉女寒冰?
Isn't it the Virgin's Ice?
当然是了!
Sure it is!
那真的发财了!
We'll be rich then!
把它卖给魔王, 我们就能拿到1000万美金了
If we sell it to the King of Evil, we'll get 10 millions
我盘算过了
I've got another idea
饮了寒冰水会长生不老!
I want to do our own business!
那么我就可以化整为零, 卖些冰水给那些有钱人
Melt it and mix it with water, sell it to those rich old man
给他们保持青春! 这些就不止1000万了, 对吧?
To give them ever lasting life! Then we'll get more from it, right?
好主意!
Good idea!
当然了
Sure
好是你的主意棒!
Bravo! Excellent idea!
对不起!
I'm sorry!
不能卖!
You can't sell it!
为什么不能卖?
Why not?
总之就是不能卖!
You can't sell it!
为什么?
Why?
这块冰可以帮我找到梦中情人
It can help me to search for my dream lover
如果谁想卖它的话, 我会和他同归于尽的
Who is going to sell it, I'll kill him
你千万不要死!
Don't!
坏了! 你干爹把脑子冻坏了!
Shit! He's got crazy!
现在我们培养情绪来骗他,行吗?
Let's prepared ourselves to cheat him, OK?
我们想过了，为了你的梦
For your dream
为了你的情人
For your lover
为了我们的友谊
For our friendship
我们宁愿不要钱...
We prefer supporting you...
也要支持你!
to the money!
有朋友真好!
What a real friend!
万岁!
Fantastic!
前面骑在冰上的人, 你们被包围了!
The three on the ice, you're surrounded!
放下那块冰,
Drop the Ice,
否则就杀了你们!
or you'll be killed!
什么事?
What's it?
放下冰
Drop the Ice
走!
Go!
放下那块冰
Drop the Ice
别想抢我们的冰! 我们走!
You can't rob our Ice! Let's go!
放下那块冰!
Drop it!
他们好像无处不在啊!
They've no time to listen!
我们进去森林吧!
Let's go to the forest!
他们依然还在!
They all hear it!
停...
Stop...
我刚才那么大的声音,
I shouted so loud that,
你猜他们会不会进来森林呢?
would they chase after us to the forest?
或许不会吧!
I don't think so!
走!
Let's go!
站稳了!
Keep your balance!
博士干爹!
Doctor!
别走!
Don't go!
现在你能把他们怎么样?
Are you giving order?
多事!
You are nosy!
别走!
Don't go!
照顾好干爹博士!
Take care of God father!
上来!
Come up!
有胆就上来
Come up if you've guts
快转旋风腿
Quick Whirl-wind
来啊!
Come on!
你们在干什么? 吓我吗?
What are you doing? Scaring me?
鬼影拳!
It's Ghost-shadow Fists!
想杀死我啊?
You want to kill me?
让我用放大镜来试一试!
I will treat you the Super Microscope!
超级放大镜!
Super Microscope!
升龙拳!
Sing Long Fists!
超级重拳!
Super Fists!
我的冰在哪里?
Where is my Ice?
情人, 他们抢走了那块冰!
Ching Yan, they robbed the Ice!
情人，把冰给我
Give me the Ice
你们先走!
You'd better leave first!
别过来!
Don't come over!
放下它
Drop it
该死!
Damn it!
加速
Increase the speed
情人干爹，那块冰是假的!
That is a fake one made by Doctor!
下来吧!
Come down!
是真的吗?
Do you mean it?
是的, 他在飞机那里等我们, 快点!
Yes, he is waiting us in the plane, hurry up!
走了!
Let's go now!
启程!
Let's go!
那块冰在哪儿? 干爹博士把它放在哪儿了?
Where is the Ice? Did Doctor take it?
他知道
He did
哪儿?
Where is it?
我怎么知道?
How do I know?
我把它隐形了!
I make it invisible!
谢谢
Thank you
到底这是块普通的冰,
Isn't it an ordinary ice,
又或者它隐藏着我梦中情人的线索呢?
or it contains the secret of my dream lover?
你告诉我!
Please tell me!
你告诉啦!
情人
Ching Yan
难道精诚所致，金石为开?
Is the Ice touched by my sincerity?
这边!
This way!
是我打开你的门
It's your door which is touched by me
上次你离开的时候,
When you left me last time,
留了封情信
you left a love letter
我看完了后实在太感动了
I was touched after reading it
我可没有给情信你啊
I didn't send you any love letter
你来做什么呢?
What do you want to do here?
做什么啊? 我都没做过什么!
Do? I haven't done anything!
哦，你想我做点什么吧?
You want me to do that?
你干什么灭灯?
Why did you turn off the light?
我害羞嘛!
I feel shy!
我更怕
Me too
大家都看不到
No one can see it
太黑了! 什么都不能做!
It's so dark! We can do nothing!
她去哪儿了?
Where is he going?
对不起!
Sorry!
别走! 不要藏起来嘛!
Don't go! Don't hide up!
你找不到我的
You can't find me in darkness
下来!
Come down!
小姐!
Miss!
我宁死不屈!
I won't surrender!
你好狠心!
You are too hard-hearted!
小姐!
Miss!
我对你这么好,
I treat you so good,
想不到你对我这么绝情
I can't imagine you are so cool to me
更想不到我不想离开这间屋子
I can't imagine I don't want to leave this room
你为什么要逼我离开呢?
Why do you want me to leave?
我还想不到的是我真的走出这间屋子
I can't imagine that I am willing to leave this room
实在太多想不到的事情发生了
So many things that are unexpected
ruby 说得对!
Ruby is right!
这个世界有太多事是我们想不到的
So many things are unexpected in this world
能够得到这块玉女寒冰
To get this Virgin's Ice
是我想不到的
It's out of my expectation
但是姑姑,
But about Madam,
难道我对你的爱,
about my love to you,
你真的一点都想不到吗?
can you even feel a little bit of it?
没道理! 真没道理!
It's pointless! It's not reasonable!
造反了?
Want a riot?
我不是 ruby
I am not Ruby
你想要的那块玉女寒冰,
Your Virgin's Ice,
现在在生命终站
it is now in the Life Terminal
我可以长生不老了!
I can live forever!
我可以更加美丽了!
I will be beautiful!
出发!
Let's go!
情人!
It's Ching Yan!
干爹!
God-father!
别理我!
Forget about me!
博士, 接住它
Doctor, take it
到底发生什么事?
What happened?
怎么会这样?
What a mess is it?
何方鼠辈? 够胆前来?
Who are you? How dare you come?
不要乱来
Don't get mad
走, 快点!
Go, hurry up!
添仔, 走!
Tim, go!
我们该怎么办?
What shall we do now?
如果不想死的话, 就放下那块冰
If you don't want to die, drop the ice
我们到底给不给他?
Shall we listen to him?
平时怎么就不见你问我的意见呢?
Why don't you ask for my opinion in other matters?
趁他没注意，你们先隐形走好了
Since he is not paying attention to us, make it invisible first
我在这里先顶着
I will block their way
别让他们走
Don't let them go
添仔, 打开那扇门, 快点!
Tim, open the door, quick!
不行啊, 回头吧!
It can't help, turn back!
死了, 我被他们抓住了
Shit, I am caught by them
情人, 快点来救我!
Ching Yan, save me!
等一下
Hold it
放开他们!
Let them go!
该死!
Damn it!
放开他们!
Let them go!
你把冰给我, 我就放了他们!
Give me the Ice, then I will let them go!
damn!
Damn!
我呸!
我也呸!
Shit!
怎么就坏了! 我已经搞定了啊!
No big deal! I have fixed them up!
可是冰被他们抢走了
The Ice is robbed by them
是啊! 是啊!
Yes! Yes!
把冰还来!
Give me back the Ice!
现在冰在我手上, 你们就没利用价值了
I have got the Ice now, you are useless to me then
下地狱吧!
Go to hell!
你没事吧?
Are you fine?
我没事
I am alright
你真没用!
You are useless!
让你们见识我胃酸的厉害!
Try the gastric juice of mine!
我吸!
I suck!
小心!
Be careful!
情人, 救我们!
Ching Yan, save us!
干爹博士!
Doctor!
好热!
It's hot!
我要烧死你们!
I want to burn you to death!
没办法了!
No way!
支持住!
Hold on!
用力啊!
Use some force!
干爷爷博士, 姑姑现身了!
Doctor, Madam appears!
情人
Ching Yan
帮我...
Help me...
玉女寒冰?
The Virgin's Ice?
把真气给我!
Give me the "Essence Air"!
我是不会把真气给你这个残暴的魔王的!
I won't give it to a cruel monster like you!
不给! 我就把你们杀光
No! I will kill you one by one
快点带情人走!
Take Ching Yan away, hurry up!
你不给真气我，我就霸王硬上弓了
If you don't give me the "Essence Air", I will take it myself
干爹，你吃点吧
Eat this, God-father
你怎么样?
How are you?
这些药没什么用啊
The medicine isn't that good to him
有没有其他的药?
Do you have another type?
其他的?
Another type?
快点
Hurry up
有, 有一些
Yes, I have some others
先吃这些吧
Just try this
我用不上了
I don't want it
在这里了
Here it is
干爹, 吃吧
Come on, take this
吃了吧, 这是灵芝草
Eat it, it's Gyrophora
没用的
It's useless
快点吃吧
Come on, take this
留下以备不时之需吧
Save it when it is needed
我知道没用, 但是可以先熬一段时间
I know it's useless, but it can last for a short time
干爷爷博士很厉害的,
Doctor is great,
他一定能救你的
he will save you
我没用, 我没办法
I am useless, I have no idea
以前你怎么就什么办法都有!
You always have many inventions!
现在, 你就什么办法都没有!
Now, you have not even one solution!
我不管!
I won't care!
你再想不到办法的话, 干爹就会死
If you can't think out any method, he will die
快点想办法!
Think out some ways!
添仔, 人总是会死的
Tim, man will die anyway
况且我比你大这么多,
I am older than you,
我肯定会在你前面死的
I will die before you
我更老, 为什么不让我先死呢?
I am even older, why don't I die before you?
不要, 别这么说...
Buy, anyway...
是我多事, 是我贪心
It's me who is nosy, it's me who is greedy for money
如果我不贪心,
If not,
我们就不会去找冰
we would not go for the Ice
你就不会见到你的梦中情人
You would not have met your dream lover
你就不会死了
You would not die
别哭!
Don't cry!
在这个世界上,
In this world,
有多少人能在临死之前可以...
how many people can fine his dream...
找到自己的梦呢?
before his death?
我就是其中的一个
Luckily, I am one of them
我太高兴了!
I am too happy!
我要多谢你
I want to thank you
你不要死!
Don't die!
其实我最不舍得的
I miss you most
就是你们两个!
I miss you two!
添仔, 在我离开后
Tim, after my death
你要自己照顾好自己. 知道不
You should take care of yourself. Got it
还记得龙卷旋风脚吗?
Do you remember the morning exercise?
不记得!
No!
没干爹陪我我什么都不记得
I won't remember if you are not with me
你不可以这样的
You can't do that
我再教你一次
I will teach you once more
你跟我做
Follow me
扶住我, 过来
Hold me, come on
准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
好了
Yes
你一天比一天更厉害了
You are getting smarter and smarter
博士干爹, 有件事我很遗憾
Doctor, I feel regret for one thing
我和添仔从来都没合过影
Tim and I haven't taken any picture together
你帮我们照一张吧?
Can you take a picture for us?
麻烦了！来吧
Please! Come on
准备好?
Ready?
给我看看!
Let me take a look!
为什么? 为什么会这样?
Why? Why?
干爹, 起来啊!
Get up, God-father!
干爹，你起来, 不要丢下我们!
Get up, don't leave us!
干爹...
God-father...
都是你的错!
It's your fault!
你赔我干爹!
Give me back my God-father!
别激动, 你干爹已经走了!
Stay calm, your God-father has just passed away!
干爹死了, 我也去陪他
Since he is dead, I want to accompany him
我已经将真气给了情人
I have sent him the "Essence Air"
你是说...
You mean the air...
魔王想千方设百计想得到的真气?
which the King of Evil wants by all means?
没错, 他很快就会醒来
Yes, he will soon recover
那么你以后就可以同干爹在一起了!
So you can stay with God-father forever!
以后?
Forever?
没了真气我就没生命力
The Essence Air means my life
我好快就会死了
I will die soon
姑姑!
Madam!
如果情人知道, 他会很伤心的
If Ching Yan knows it, he will be very upset
他醒来后, 有真气护身,
When he wakes up, he is protected by the Essence Air,
就会刀枪不入的了
nothing can harm him
但是他还不是魔王的对手, 别让他去
But he can't defeat the King of Evil, don't let him go
那你怎么样?
How are you?
不要让他见到我!
Don't let him see me!
一切都是为了爱
All because of "Love"
姑姑...
Madam...
干爹博士呢?
Where is Doctor?
干爹博士, 添仔!
Doctor, Tim!
我知道你们在这里!
I know you are here!
出来! 出来啊!
Come out! Come out!
好啊，你们不想出来是吗?
Don't you want to come out?
我就在这里等你们
I will wait you here
I will wait till you come out!
出来告诉我知道...
Until you tell me...
姑姑在那里为止
where my Madam is
大家都别想吃!
We won't have food!
如果你们不告诉我姑姑在哪里,
If you don't tell me where Madam is,
我就要你们不能睡好,吃好!
I won't let you sleep, I won't let you eat!
出来!
Come out!
我好饿啊!
I am hungry!
我们投降!
Surrender!
我们斗不过真心!
We can't compete with the power of love!
不准吃!
No!
这样吧, 你们告诉我姑姑在哪里
Well, tell me where Madam is
我就让你们吃!
Then I will let you eat!
你想要姑姑? 我满头都是菇菇!
You want woman? I can find you some!
告诉我!
Tell me!
情人, 放松点!
Ching Yan, take it easy!
不就是个梦嘛!
It's just a dream!
为了个梦, 为了姑姑,
For your dream, for your madam,
你差点赔上自己的命!
you have nearly lost your life!
我们为了姑姑也不得安宁!
Your Madam have made us in a mess too!
你说是不是?
Do you agree?
是啊...
Yes...
自杀?
Suicide?
如果你们不告诉我姑姑在哪里,
If you don't tell me where she is,
我就马上死在你们面前
I prefer dying in front of you
你一定会后悔的
You will regret it
姑姑可能在里面
She may be inside
朋友, 虽然忠言逆耳,
Pal, although the truth may hurt you,
听我说, 别再寻你的梦了
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
谢谢
Thank you
你们让开!
Get lost!
朋友, 虽然忠言逆耳,
Pal, although the truth may hurt you,
听我说, 别再寻你的梦了
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
走开啦!
Get lost!
朋友, 虽然忠言逆耳,
Pal, although the truth may hurt you,
听我说, 别再寻你的梦了
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
走开啦,
Get lost,
朋友, 虽然忠言逆耳,
pal, although the truth may hurt you,
听我说, 别再寻你的梦了
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
走开!
Get lost!
姑姑
Madam
你走吧, 她不会再见你的
Go now, she won't see you
为什么?
Why?
发生什么事情了?
What happened?
你告诉我吧
Tell me please
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
如果你见到她, 你都不会再爱她的
If you see her again, you may not love her anymore
不会
No
无论她变成什么样子,
No matter how she is changed,
无论发生什么事情,
no matter what has happened,
我都一样爱她, 这个就是事实
I love her, this is the truth
你进来
Come in
婆婆, 你看一下
Granny, look
这里收藏着我所有梦的讯息
These are the information about my dreams
从我出世开始
From the day I was born
每晚, 我都会梦见姑姑
Every night, I see Madam in my dream
我们一起长大
We grew up together
一起上学读书
We went to school together
一起相爱
We love each other
我们都好爱对方
We fall deeply for each other
直到我们结婚, 我发过誓!
Till we get marry, I swear!
就算她到了80岁
Even she is 80 years old
我依然是那么爱她
I still love her
我想你一定很明白我的心!
I think you understand my heart!
你是姑姑
You are Madam
姑姑!
Madam!
那么你现在还爱不爱我?
Do you still love me?
你嫁给我吧!
Marry me!
太感动了!
I am really touched!
不要问我
一生曾经爱过多少人
你不懂我伤有多深
要剥开伤口总是很残忍
劝你别做痴心人
多情暂且保留几分
不喜欢孤独
却又害怕两个人相处
这分明是一种痛苦
在人多时候最沉默
笑容也寂寞
在万丈红尘中啊
找个人爱我
当我避开你的柔情苦泪开始坠落
是不敢不想不应该再谢谢你的爱
我不得不存在啊
像一颗尘埃还是会带给你伤害
上次我象魔王告密是我不对
I was wrong to tell the King of Evil where the Virgin's Ice was
但是, 这次,
But, this time,
我好大方带来货礼来祝贺他们新婚,
I am so generous to send them present for their wedding,
我想情人一定会原谅我的
I think Ching Yan will forgive me
他们抓走了姑姑!
They captured Madam!
情人!
Ching Yan!
干爷爷博士, 游泳后
After the swim,
现在我的心情好多了
I feel better now
真的?
Really?
有没有搞错啊! 放炮不需要这么大的火吧?
Kidding! Why they need such a big fire for barbecue?
不是的! 干爹被人烧啊!
No! God-father is on fire!
什么? 有人烧我们的船!
What? Our ship is on fire!
干爹!
God-father!
情人!
Ching Yan!
干爹!
God-father!
让我进去!
Let me go in!
不要去! 会烧死你的!
Don't! You will be burnt!
情人, 你在哪儿?
Ching Yan, where are you?
情人, 别死啊! 不要离开我们!
Ching Yan, don't die! Don't leave us!
你们干什么?
What are you doing?
我睡得好好的!
I am sleeping!
为什么要吵醒我呢?
Why did you wake me up?
刚才船爆炸了!
The ship exploded!
你全身都是火啊!
You were burning!
什么?我被火烧？
What?
我为什么没事?
Why didn't I hurt?
姑姑!
Madam!
我想姑姑说得是真的
I wonder what Madam told us was true
我们试一下
Let's try
好!
Fine!
姑姑...你怎么样?
Madam... How are you?
我以后怎么见人啊?
How can I face others?
我的脸肯定烧坏了!
My face is ruined!
无论你变成什么样子,
No matter how you changed,
我都一样爱你啊，姑姑
I still love you
我的天, 我的脸花成什么样子了!
My God, my face is ruined!
让我看看!
Let me have a look!
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是 ruby
I am Ruby
是你啊，你怎么会扮成我姑姑呢?
Why did you pretend to be Madam?
我只不过想...
I just want...
别说那么多了, 我先帮你医好你的脸
Cut the crap, let me cure your face first
行不行的?
Can you?
行!
Sure!
让我来
Let me try
真的没受伤!
He is not hurt!
真的伤不了他!
He is fine!
你们干什么呢?
What are you doing?
没什么, 练下功夫
Nothing, just practise Kung-fu
情人!
Ching Yan!
姑姑被魔王捉走了
Madam is caught by the King of Evil
杀了我吧!
Kill me!
如果魔王知道真气在你这里,
If he knows the "Essence Air" is kept with you,
他一定会引你救姑姑的
he will tempt you to save Madam
你一个人去好危险
It's dangerous for you to go alone
无论怎样, 能够救姑姑做什么我都愿意
I don't care, I just want to save Madam
希望你们两个
I hope you can help me
守住魔宫出口, 一个都别放走
Guard the exit of the Evil's Palace, don't let anyone go out
那么你要小心啊
You should take care
我不管你是谁
I don't care who you are
如果你不放了我姑姑
If you don't hand me my Madam
我就让你死无葬身之地
I want you to die terribly
你果然大胆!
You do have guts!
把真气给我
Give the "Essence Air" back to me
把姑姑还给我, 我就放你一马
Give me back my wife, and I will let you go
有胆子你就跟我进深渊
Come to the Horrible Valley with me if you have guts
该死!
Damn it!
姑姑!
Madam!
姑姑...
Madam...
你等我啊, 姑姑
Wait for me, Madam
干爷爷博士, 快点亲他!
Doctor, kiss him!
干爹, 快点把真气还给姑姑
God-father, give Madam the Essence Air
情人!
Ching Yan!
姑姑!
Madam!
不够长啊, 再长点!
It's not long enough, longer!
快点救姑姑!
Save Madam, quick!
情人!
Ching Yan!
帮我!
Help me!
好, 魔王死了!
Bravo, the King of Evil is killed!
好啊!
Bravo!
情人!
Ching Yan!
快点走, 这里马上就会爆炸了!
Go now, he will soon explode!
情人!
Ching Yan!
你怎么样? 回答我啊!
How are you? Answer me please!
情人!
Ching Yan!
我还没死!
I am still alive!
在我没真正见到姑姑之前,
Before I meet Madam,
我是不会死的!
I won't die!
你跟梦里面真的一模一样
You are the same as you are in my dream
你这又何苦呢!
It's not necessary for you to do so!
你知道吗?
Do you know?
世界上有一种蝴蝶,
There is a butterfly,
它只能活24小时, 可谓是朝生暮死
it can live only 24 hours, it is born in the morning, and die at night
它活着只是为了寻找它的另一半,
It lives for finding its better half,
你现在明白吧?
understand?
是我自愿的
I am willing to do so
干爹...
God-father...
情人!
Ching Yan!
我救了他
I saved him
他又救回我
He saved me too
可惜世间只有一口真气
The Essence Air is enough for one person only
我们怎样才能共享呢?
How can we share it?
我应该怎么样做呢?
What shall I do?
把他交给我
Give him to me
从那天后
From that day onwards
我们就再也没见到他们
We have never seen them
因为姑姑将情人...
Because she sent Ching Yan...
送到一个世界上至阴至寒的地方
to the coldest place of the world
来保护情人的性命
To keep his life
不知道他们现在在哪儿呢?
Do you know where are they?
听说有探险家在南极见到一对情侣,
An adventurer did see a couple near the cliff in the South Pole,
我想那就是他们吧
I think they are the couple mentioned